- Hi, I'm Clara.
-嗨，我是克拉拉
I work in product marketing on the Gemini app at Google.
我在 Google 的 Gemini 應用程序上從事產品營銷。
Now, when I'm having high-stakes conversations,
現在，當我進行高風險的對話時，例
like sales pitches, presentations, or difficult one-on-ones,
如銷售推介、簡報或困難的一對一對一時，
it's crucial that I'm able to perform my best,
我必須能夠表現最好的表現，
really deliver the points that I need to make
真正提出我需要提出的觀點，並具有說服力十分重要
and be persuasive.
。
In this video, we're gonna use Gemini Live
在這個視頻中，我們將使用 Gemini Live 模擬具有
to simulate a challenging conversation
挑戰性的對話，
and get feedback on how we did.
並獲得關於我們的工作方式的反饋。
Now, to access Gemini Live,
現在，要訪問 Gemini Live，
you'll need to download the Gemini mobile app on your phone.
您需要在手機上下載 Gemini 移動應用程序。
When we use Gemini Live, we're not prompting,
當我們使用 Gemini Live 時，我們不是提示，我
we're having a natural, free-flowing conversation.
們正在進行自然，自由流暢的對話。
Let's say I wanted to practice a sales pitch
假設我想與潛在
with a potential customer.
客戶一起練習銷售推廣。
I'll show you what that looks like.
我會告訴你它是什麼樣的。
To start, click into Live.
若要開始，請按一下「即時」。
Hey, Gemini, I need to make an important sales call.
嘿雙子座我需要打個重要的銷售電話
Let's role-play.
讓我們扮演角色扮演吧。
- That's a great idea.
-這是個好主意
What kind of product are you selling?
您在銷售什麼樣的產品？
- So I'm a salesperson for a logistics company
-所以我是一家名為紙板大車的物流公司
called Cardboard Caravan.
的銷售員。
My goal is to book a meeting
我的目標是與
with the logistics manager at Terry's Trousers,
Terry's Trousers 的物流經理預約會議，他最
who recently submitted an inquiry on our website.
近在我們的網站上提交了詢問。
I call and you answer the phone.
我打電話，你接電話
- Got it.
-明白了
I'm ready to play the logistics manager at Terry's Trousers.
我準備好擔任特里褲子的物流經理了
Let's do this.
讓我們這樣做。
Thank you for calling Terry's Trousers.
謝謝你打電話給特里的褲子
How may I direct your call?
我該如何指導你的電話？
- Hi, this is Clara from Cardboard Caravan.
-嗨，我是紙板車廂的克拉拉
I'm calling to follow up on an inquiry
我正在打電話跟進您在我們的
you submitted on our website.
網站上提交的詢問。
Could you tell me a little bit
您能告訴我一下您希
about what you're hoping to achieve
望通過
with a new logistics partner?
新的物流合作夥伴實現什麼？
- Absolutely, Clara.
-當然克拉拉我
We're looking for a logistics partner
們正在尋找一個可以幫助
who can help us streamline our shipping process
我們簡化運輸流程
and reduce costs.
並降低成本的物流合作夥伴。
We've been experiencing some delays
我們最近遇到一些延誤
and inefficiencies lately,
和效率不足，我們需要
and we need a reliable solution
一個可靠的解決方案來
to ensure our trousers get to our customers on time.
確保我們的褲子準時送達客戶。
- I totally understand.
-我完全明白
We've helped other companies in your position.
我們已經幫助您位置的其他公司。
Would you be open to a brief follow-up meeting
您願意參加簡短的跟進會議，
to talk about how we could help you specifically?
討論我們如何特別為您提供幫助？
- I'm sure that could be arranged.
-我相信可以安排
What times are you available for a meeting?
您在什麼時候可以參加會議？
- How about next week?
-下週怎麼樣？
I can follow up via email and send you a case study?
我可以通過電子郵件跟進並向您發送個案研究？
- Sure. Next week works.
-當然下週工作。
Please send the case study.
請發送案例研究。
- Now that we finished our Live conversation,
-現在我們完成了實時對話後，我們
we can ask Gemini for feedback.
可以要求雙子座提供反饋。
We'll ask Gemini to provide feedback on my approach,
我們將要求 Gemini 對我的方法提供反饋，
includes strengths, weaknesses,
包括優勢、弱
and suggestions for improvement.
點和改進建議。
Huh.
嗯。
Wow.
哇
There's some great feedback in here
這裡有一些很棒的反饋
that I can definitely use to practice.
，我肯定可以用來練習。
I also use this feature to talk through ideas,
我還使用此功能來討論想法，
and then turn those into actionable project proposals.
然後將這些想法轉換為可行的項目提案。
Say I have an out-of-the-box concept
假設我有一個開箱即用的
for a new product launch.
新產品發布的概念。
I'll ask Gemini Live to help me flesh out the concept,
我會要求 Gemini Live 幫助我實現這個概念，然後將
and then synthesize our conversation into an action plan
我們的對話合成一個行動計劃，我可
that I can share with my leadership
以與我的領導者分享，
and with clearly-outlined next steps.
並明確概述的後續步驟。
It's a great way to go from idea to execution.
這是從構想到執行的好方法。
So the next time you want another perspective
因此，下次您想要另一個角度
or help with ideation,
或幫助構想時，請
try going Live with Gemini.
嘗試與雙子座一起生活。